Guide to the Cornell University International Agriculture records, 1952-1980.
Cornell University International Agriculture records
- Series XIII. University of the Philippines - Cornell University Graduate Education Program(UP-Cornell) - Chronological File
  - Talk by President James Perkins at UPCA, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Everett Report, June-December, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, 1965-1968 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    Consists mainly of the correspondence of Charles Palm, Harry Case, President Umali, and K.L. Turk
  - Talk by Henry Case Before the Manila Rotary Club, March 10, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Filipino Assistants - Allowances, August-September, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Discussion with Dr. G. Gant and Dr. David Pfanner (from the Ford Foundation), Regarding UP-Cornell Graduate Education Program in the Philippines, October, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - UP-Cornell Notes - K.L. Turk, 1966-1967 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Research Guidelines for UP-Cornell Graduate Students, 1966-1969 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Dean Charles Palm, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - UP-Cornell Budget, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - UP-Cornell Ford Foundation Review, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - K.L. Turk Conferences with Mr. Staples and Mr. Quinn, 1967-1970 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Dr. Bloom Budget Notes - K.L. Turk, 1967-1970 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    Folder dated 1967-1970, notes inside the folder dated "1969?"
  - UP-Cornell Staff, 1967-1971 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Barton Report: Review of the UP-Cornell Program, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - UP-Cornell Notes - K.L. Turk, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Report on the Mindanao Study Trip, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Post Report: The Philippines by the Ford Foundation, October, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - UP-Cornell Budget, 1968-1970 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - UP-Cornell Notes - K.L. Turk, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - UPCA Budget, 1969-1970 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - UP-Cornell Notes - K.L. Turk, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - UP-Cornell Notes - K.L. Turk, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Notes for Dean Palm, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Director of Graduate Studies Report, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Former Graduate Assistants UP-Cornell, 1971-1972 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - UP-Cornell Notes - K.L. Turk, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Report for Grace Period, 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - UP-Cornell Notes - K.L. Turk, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Retrospective Evaluation of a Foreign Aid Project: The Case of Los Banos(UPCA), 1973 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Proposal - University of Ibadan, 1969-1972 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Proposal - University of Ibadan, 1969-1972 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Elmer Ewing - Ibadan Correspondence, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Robert Gilmer - Ibadan Correspondence, 1971-1974 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Loosli - Ibadan Correspondence, 1971-1975 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Fellowships - University of Ibadan, 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - International Symposium on Animal Production, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence - Financial, 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Ethopia - Haile Sellassie I University, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - University of Ghana, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - University of Ife, Ibadan, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Uganda - Makerere University, 1967-1970 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Uganda - Makerere University, 1967-1970 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Uganda - Ministry of Agriculture and Economic Development, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Visiting Faculty - University of Nigeria, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Observations and Appraisals of Educational and Research Program - Makerere and Ibadan, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Scientific Projects for Africa, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - African Trip - Cline, Stanton, Turk, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Guide to the Federal Department of Agricultural Research, Nigeria, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Strategy For the Conguest of Hunger Symposium - Rockefeller Foundation, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Report from Rockefeller Foundation - India, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Uganda - Makerere University, 1967-1970 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Association of U.S. University Directors of International Agricultural Programs, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Potential Increases in Food Supply Through Research in Agriculture, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - U.P. Cornell Graduate Education Program Terminal Report, 1963-1972 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Research Highlights - International Rice Research Institute, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - United Nations University, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - CGIAR - Consultative Group on International Agricultural Research, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - International Research in Agriculture, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Cornell Peace Corps Intern Program, 1968-1972 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Cornell Peace Corps Intern Program, 1968-1972 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Aggie Green and Gold, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Extension - FHDO, 1964-1974 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - ACAP Newsletter, 1972-1974 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - AAACI Newsletter, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Agricultural Planning - Ford Foundaton, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - AID - Manila, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Autonomy of UPLB, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Dairy Training and Research Institute - Los Banos, 1963-1967 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Dairy Training - Philippines Final Report, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - ESSO Pamphlets, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Food and Drug Administration in Philippines, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Forestry Proposal, 1964-1965 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Land Reform - Philippines, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Library Conference - Ford, 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Marcos Martial Law, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Agriculture Research in the Philippines (R. M. Lantican), 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Philippines Agricultural Research System Review, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Philippine Recommends Pamphlets, 1969-1972 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Corn Program, 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Advanced Training and Research for Corn, Sorghum, and other Upland Crops Production, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Mungo Program, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - PCAR, 1972-1974 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Pasture Program, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Annual Report UPCA, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Rice Program, 1970-1972 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Rice Production Manual, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Rice Trials, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Rice Research Training, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Soybean Program, 1970-1972 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Sorghum Program, 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Vegetable Program, 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Unrest at Los Banos, 1968-1970 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Viability Study UPCA, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Cooperative Development of an Improved Graduate Education and Research Program - College of Agriculture, University of Philippines, 1961-1963 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Project Leader's Guide - U.P. Cornell Graduate Education Program, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Ford Foundation Grants, 1963-1971 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Cornell - Los Banos Project, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Umali - Progress Report on UPCA, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Special Review Team, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Development Program Department of Agriculture University of Philippines, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - UPCA Five Year Development Program, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Campus Plan Los Banos, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Campus Development Plan UPCA, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Landscape Development, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Final Planning Sessions for UPCO, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - U. P. Cornell Graduate Education Program, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Orientation Cornell Staff, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Endowed Administration, 1971-1976 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Keith Kennedy, 1972-1978 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Development Fund, 1973-1976 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - James Spencer, 1973-1977 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Planning and Facilities, 1974-1978 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Charles Palm, 1971-1975 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Department of Agricultural Economics, 1977-1978 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Agricultural Engineering, 1975-1978 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Agronomy, 1972-1975 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Agronomy, 1976-1978 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Nurul Islam Bhuiyan, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Animal Science, 1976-1978 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Animal Science Review, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Bailey Hortorium, 1974-1977 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Department of Communication Arts, 1973-1978 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Department of Education, 1970-1978 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Department of Entomology, 1971-1978 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Department of Entomology, 1977-1978 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Cooperative Extension, 1974-1978 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Department Of Floriculture, 1971-1978 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Food Science, 1972-1978 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Post-Harvest Food Losses, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Food Science Institute, 1970-1975 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Geneva Agricultural Experiment Station, 1971-1978 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Instruction, 1973-1978 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Mann Library, 1972-1978 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Media Services, 1975-1978 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Natural Resources, 1972-1978 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Plant Breeding, 1971-1978 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - USAID (U.S. Agency for International Development) Grant Proposal, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Department of Plant Pathology, 1971-1978 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Department of Plant Pomology, 1972-1978 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Department of Poultry Science, 1972-1977 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Research, 1971-1978 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Department of Rural Sociology, 1971-1978 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Department of Vegetable Crops, 1974-1978 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Committee of Chairmen, 1977-1978 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Dean and Directors Meeting Minutes, 1977-1978 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - (CALS) College of Agriculture and Life Sciences Meetings, 1972-1978 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence - A, 1977-1978 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - CALS Advisory Council, 1976-1978 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Agriculture International, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - ADC (Agricultural Development Council), 1977 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - American Farm School, 1977-1978 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - AUSUDIAP (Association of U.S. University Directors of International Agricultural Programs), 1976-1978 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - AUSUDIAP Annual Meetings, 1977-1978 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence - B, 1976-1978 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Bandladesh, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Biological Science in Rural Developing Nations, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Alice Browne, 1964-1978 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence C, 1976-1978 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Campus Coordinating Committee) on World Food Issues, 1976-1977 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - CIS (Center for International Studies_, 1976-1977 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - CIS Executive Committee, 1976-1978 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - CIS Grants, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - CIS Rural Development Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Rural Development Participating Project, 1977-1978 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Canadian International Development Agency, 1972-1975 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Chile, 1975-1977 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence - D, 1976-1977 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Ditchley Foundation, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence - E, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - East - West Center, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Embrapa - Brazil, 1974-1976 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - Environmental Studies, 1977-1978 (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - Exchange Programs, 1977-1978 (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence - F, 1977-1978 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Food and Agricultural Organization, 1976-1977 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Ford Foundation, 1977-1978 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Foreign Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Fulbright - Hays, 1977-1978 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence - G, 1977-1978 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Graduate School, 1970-1978 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Graduate Faculty Representatives, 1976-1978 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Graduate School Annual Reports, 1975-1977 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence - H, 1976-1977 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - University of Hawaii Proposal to Aid Vegetable Production, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Human Ecology, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence - I, 1975-1977 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - International Agricultural Development Seminar Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - India, 1977-1978 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Indonesia, 1977-1978 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Institute of International Education, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - International Agriculture Department Leaders, 1976-1978 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - International Agricultural Development Service, 1977-1978 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - International Agriciltural and Rural Development Graduate Faculty, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - International Science and Education Council, 1976-1978 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - League for International Food Education, 1976-1978 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - International Student Office, 1976-1978 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - International Visitors, 1976-1977 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence - J, 1976-1977 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence - K, 1976-1978 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Dean Kavi Chutikul, 1977-1978 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Kansas State University, 1974-1976 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Keys Seminar, 1976-1977 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence - L, 1976-1978 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Luce Foundation, 1976-1977 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence - M, 1977-1978 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - University of Minnesota, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence - N, 1976-1977 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - National Science Foundation, 1976-1977 (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - NAS (National Academy of Sciences) World Food and Nutrition Study, 1976-1977 (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges, 1976-1978 (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - North East Directors International Agriculture Development, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - Nutritional Sciences, 1977-1978 (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - NYSTROM, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence - O, 1976-1977 (Box 27, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence - P, 1976-1977 (Box 27, Folder 42)
  - Peace Corps, 1976-1978 (Box 27, Folder 43)
  - Professors at Large, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 44)
  - Program Direction Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 27, Folder 45)
  - Correspondence - Q, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 46)
  - Correspondence - R, 1976-1977 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence - S, 1976-1977 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Science, Technology and Society, 1975-1978 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Southeast Asia Regional Center Agreement, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Sigma XI International Chapter, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence - T, 1976-1978 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Tree Crops, 1975-1977 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence - U, V, 1977-1978 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - United States Department of Agriculture, 1976-1978 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - United Nations Development Program, 1976-1977 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - United Nations Educational, Scientific and Cultural Organizaton, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence - W, 1977-1978 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - University of the West Indies, 1977-1979 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence - X, Y, Z, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Travel Vouchers, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - International Agricultural Research Centers, 1972-1976 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - International Agricultural Research Centers Week, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - International Agricultural Research Centers Week, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Asian Vegetable Research and Development Center, 1972-1975 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Asian Vegetable Research and Development Center Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Asian Vegetable Research and Development Center Publications, 1972-1975 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - International Center for Tropical Agriculture, 1971-1978 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - International Center for Agricultural Research in Dry Areas, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - International Center of Insect Physiology and Ecology, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - International Crops Research Institute for the Semi-Arid Tropics, 1975-1976 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - International Institute for Tropical Agriculture, 1971-1976 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - International Livestock Center for Africa, 1970-1974 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - International Laboratory for Research on Animal Diseases, 1973-1974 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - International Laboratory for Research on Animal Diseases, 1973-1974 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - International Maize and Wheat Improvement Center, 1971-1975 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - CIMMYT (Centro Internacional de Mejoramiento de Maiz y Trigo), 1973-1978 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - CIMMYT Publications, 1973-197 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - International Potato Center, 1976-1977 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - International Potato Research Center, 1969-1977 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - (IRRI) International Rice Research Institute Corresponcence, 1963-1977 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Report to IRRI, 1973-1978 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - IRRI (Brady), 1973-1977 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - IRRI Publications, 1973-1974 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - International Potato Center Newsletter, 1972-1974 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - International Potato Center Publications, 1970-1972 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - International Vegetable Research Institute for the Tropics, 1974-1975 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Tropical Agricultural Research and Training Center - CATIE, 1973-1976 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - West Africa Rice Development Association, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Institutional Development Agreement, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - A.I.D. (Agency for International Development) Workshop, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - A.I.D. General Correspondence, 1972-1977 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - A.I.D. Employment, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - A.I.D. Basic Agreement - Cornell University, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - A.I.D. NASULGC (National Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges) Relations, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - A.I.D. Bulletins, 1966-1972 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - A.I.D. USDA Training, 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - A.I.D. Participant Training Grant, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Directory of Institutional Resources Supported by 211 (d) Grants, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - A.I.D. Employment, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - U.S. A.I.D. 211 (d) Annual Reports, 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - U.S. A.I.D. 211 (d) Annual Reports, 1970-1974 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Soil Training Research Grant AID 211 (d), 1971-1977 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Consortium on Soils of the Tropics Proposed Renewal, 1977-1978 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - A.I.D. Employment, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Proposal for Establishing International Tropical Soils Network Center, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Soils of the Tropics, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Center Director's Meeting - Arlington, Va., 1977 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Soils Resources Inventories Workshop, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - A.I.D. Tropical and Subtropical Agriculture Research and Training, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Annual Report University Consortium on the Soils of the Tropics, 1971-1972 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - 211 (d) Tropical Soils Executive Committee Meeting, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - AID Review of 211 (d) Grant - Tropical Soils, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Cooperative Program for Research and Training in Tropical Soils - Washington, 1970 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - 211 (d) Project on Tropical Soils - Washington, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Annual Review - Soils of the Tropics - Washington, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Consortium on Tropical Soils - Washington, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Soils Training and Research Grant, 1968-1970 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Soils Training and Research Grant, 1970-1973 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Development of Soy-Based Foods, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Soil Research for Development of Food Crops of the Tropics, 1969-1970 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Soil Research for Development of Food Crops of the Tropics, 1971-1972 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Tropical Soils Institute, 1972-1973 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - AID - Agriculture Education Planning - Nepal, 1972-1977 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - AID - Niger, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - AID - Pakistan, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - AID - Interregional Research and Development Program, 1971-1972 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - AID - Project on Pest Disease Management, 1971-1972 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - AID - Project on Pest Disease Management, 1972-1976 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Professor Mai - Pest Management Project, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Minutes of Advisory Group on Pest Management, 1971-1972 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - AID - Proposed Project on Pest Disease Management, 1970-1971 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - AID - Proposed Project on Pest Disease Management, 1971-1972 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - AID - Proposed Project on Pest Disease Management, 1970 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - AID - Proposed Project on Pest Disease Management, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - AID - Sahel Development Program, 1974-1978 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - AID - Tanzania, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - AID - International Nutrition and Development Policy, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - AID - Science, Technology and Development, 1971-1975 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - AID - Visiting Professors, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Handbook Country Contracting, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Economic Growth Trends - Near East, South Asia, East Asia, Latin America, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Agency for International Development - Submission to Congress Summary, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Agency for International Development - Submission to Congress - Middle East, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Agency for International Development - Submission to Congress - Asia Programs, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Agency for International Development - Submission to Congress - Near East Programs, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Advisees - Oyer, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - East-West Center Cooperative Agreement - Crawford, 1972-1973 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Graduate School, 1963-1968 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - SMIS (Statutory Management Information System Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Deans and Directors, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Agricultural College and University Development Workshop, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Agricultural College and University Development Workshop, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Conference on Role of Animal Agriculture Meeting World Food Needs - Washington, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - NASULGC, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - NASULGC Annual Meeting, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Agricultural Development Council - Wharton, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - AID - East Pakistan University, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Iniversidade Federal Rural do Rio Grande do Sul, 1967-1972 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - International Communications Workshop, 1972-1978 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - International Communications Workshop, 1972-1978 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Cornell Latin American YEAR, 1965-1971 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Cornell Workshop on Some Emerging Issues Accompaning Recent Breakthroughs in Food Production, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Ford Foundation Grant, 1967-1972 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - University of Costa Rica Proposal for AID, 1972 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Education and World Affairs Advisory Group, 1966-1968 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - IAD Programs Executive Committee - Ford Foundation, 1966-1967 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Ford Foundation Agriculture Development in Latin America, 1965 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Interim Grant to Support Education and Research in Agricultural Sciences, 1964-1968 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - India Agriculture into the 1970's, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Ulysses Grant, 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - In K. Han, 1965-1973 (Box 33, Folder 17)